naukriform.in 2017-03-11

# Privacy policy - NaukriForm.in

The privacy of our blog or website known as **www.naukriform.in** is very significant to all those who opened this page regularly, for getting all information about latest Jobs (Sarkari Naukri). If you want more Information or have any query about our privacy policy, so you can share with us without any hesitation by contact us link. We assure you that your personal details will not be forwarded to anyone.

The blog provides you the entire details about what privacy policy we follow, if the seekers asked any question on this site we will reply you very quickly our staff know that privacy of your personal information is very important for all the seekers.

This Privacy policy outline the type of individual information is received and collected by naukriform.in and how it is used.

**Log Files**

The details inside the log files includes IP (internet protocol) addresses/type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP) date/time stamp/ referring/exit pages& no. of clicks to analyze trends, IP addresses

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

www.naukriform.in use cookies to save info about visitor’s preferences, record user-detailed on which pages the user access or visit, to customize Advertisements.

**Double-click DART Cookie**

Google, as a 3rd party purveyor uses cookies to serve ads on our website. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it, to serve ads to users which are according to their visit on www.naukriform.in and other sites on the Internet. Some of our advertising partners may use cookies. Our website “naukriform.in” does not have any control over these cookies that are used by third party or other party.

Google Adsense  
Infolinks

The third party can ad-serves or add networks use advertisement cookies and log file for different technologies to the advertisements and links that appear on _[www.naukriform.in](http://www.naukriform.in/)_ in send directly to your browser.

Every step has been taken just to make the accuracy of information safe appointed in this site knows as naukriform.in it does not accept any accountability for any loss to any person for the results of any action taken on the basis of this information. If you are interested to disable cookies, you may do so by your own browser option.

Share this useful info...
